While we were dealing
with the rebellion issue...
...the infidels caught us off guard.
If you had not come in
time, Karesi Bey, many alps...
...would become martyrs, and
Karadin would become an infidel land.
What else could I do, Begum Hatun?
The infidels were attacking
the land of the Turks.
How could Karesi Bey ignore that?
Karadin is Osman Bey's property after all.
And we know about the troubles between you.
Anyone else would ignore it.
I am not anyone else, son.
I am Karesi Bey.
Osman Bey says that I work with infidels...
...and that I make evil plans.
Even when he speaks like that...
...and accuses me of being selfish...
...our conflict shall not overshadow
the cause of Turks.
Even if it's Osman Beys property...
...the lands watered with martyrs blood...
...are more important than anything.
Also, Osman Bey is younger than me.
Of course I will protect
the lands he can't protect...
And keep the Beys and alps he controls...
...alive.
Thank you, Karesi Bey.
Thank you.
Where are you going Gonca?
You disobeyed me!
You burned me, Gonca!
You asked for this!
You have nowhere to go.
I have no baby either.
Ever since the first time I saw you...
...I have been in love
with you, trickster hatun.
Only you, Alaeddin.
My love.
My test.
My homeland.
Only you, madrasah student.
From now on..
...I will just live for you.
For us.
I will cope up with everything just for you.
Gonca Hatun?
Gulce?
What are you doing here?
I came out to get some fresh
air. What are you doing here?
We are going to wash clothes.
Okay then.
I'll accompany you.
Come on.
Come on Gulce.
We haven't seen any infidels
until we arrived at the castle.
The castle wasn't in defence order either,
my Bey.
Alps, tell me.
An army was coming for Karadin.
Haven't you heard it?
We heard it, Osman.
We heard it.
We heard it, and did what was necessary.
Karesi Bey.
Karesi Bey, yeah.
While we were taking
precautions for The Greek rebellion...
...that ignoble Lucas brought his army
to the castle, Osman Bey.
Thankfully...
...Karesi Bey saved us from a great defeat.
So Karesi Bey saved us from a big loss.
Tell me.
You have worked with the infidels...
...to plan against us each time, Karesi Bey.
Now you're the hero?
I wish to hear.
Karesi Bey's ship was near Bursa, my Bey.
He threatened Lucas to leave.
We heard the infidels was heading
towards Osman bey's land, Karadin.
We heard Osman Bey wasn't able to fight back...
...due to the riots and uprisings in his land.
The young might not respect the elder...
But the elder must
protect the young at all times.
We wished to protect your land...
...which was about to be lost.
Was that a mistake Osman?
On the contrary.
You did well.
Allah bless you.
So, you saved our Alps.
...you protected our land.
Then..
...Karadin Castle...
...and the lands surroundings it...
..are my gift to you.
So you'll give me Karadin?
Certainly....
...we...
....will return both kindness and evil.
If you're here to be our savior...
...Allah bless you.
Now...
....in return for your favor...
...this castle is yours.
Osman.
I guess you want to pay me back.
You're good at both
politics and the battlefield.
You know I have many castles.
Keep Karadin.
Be my ally.
No.
It's against the traditions to reject gifts.
Karesi Bey.
My decision is final.
Begum Hatun.
Call back your Alps now.
Karadin Castle...
...is Karesi Bey's now.
Thank you.
Yusuf. Get the horses.
Alps.
Come on.
Great father...
God...
...punished me with Karadin defeat
because I made an agreement with the Turks.
But I will never kneel, father.
Never.
I'm going to destroy Osman.
Sofia?
I'll be with you while you're
destroying Osman, Lucas.
You...
How?
I thought...
You thought I died like everybody else.
But God...
...allowed me to live.
God brought me back so I
can pass God's wrath to him.
To end the Turks.
Together...
...we'll build a great kingdom.
A great kingdom that we will water
it's grounds with the Turk's blood.
One that feeds off death.
A hungry one.
Bloodthirsty...
...hungry...
...and merciless.
Is it time for revenge?
I've waited so much for this.
What did you do? What is it that I don't know?
My bey forgive me but I don't understand.
Why did we give up the castle
we got with so many sacrifices?
My Shahzade is right my bey.
We had so many fall martyr for that land.
My bey.
Forgive me but...
...didn't you say our land is the
guarantee we have for our freedom?
Why did we give away our land my bey?
Beys!
Come to your senses.
We're managing a nation.
We...
...are taking root all over these lands.
Don't forget this.
The worst mistake that makes a nation fall...
...is the ignorance that is hidden under pride.
Tell me.
Don't you know Treaty of al-Hudaybiya?
Hadrath Omer and his companions...
...objected to our Prophet's call.
What did the infidels want with this treaty?
Tell me Boran.
They said Muslims won't be able to
perform umrah in Makkah, my bey.
See?
Why did our Prophet...
...accept this treaty which was not in favor..
...of Muslims?
Tell me Alaeddin.
That decision which was viewed as cruelty...
...was the key to Mecca's conquer, my bey.
There.
There might be evil in what
you think is good.
There may also be good in
what you think is evil.
Of course, of course, Allah
will be the light in our road.
But do you think Karasi Bey
will rule that castle in justice?
Do you think Karadin will have peace?
Osman Bey is right. You've seen
what we couldn't see, again.
He's also protected our honor by
giving Karadin to Karasi, too.
Listen to me carefully now.
It's time for revenge now.
You'll repair everywhere, after
the rebellion in Sogut is over, Orhan.
As you command, my Bey.
Bala.
Trade.
The trade of Sogut will be much better,
in fact, it will be the heart of the trade.
This will be your mission.
As you command, my Bey.
Come on, then.
Everyone back to their duty!
Kayi Tents
Hatuns, where is Gonca, have you seen her?
Have you seen her? Where is Gonca?
What's wrong, sisters? Why don't you answer?
Sister.
What happened?
Fatma.
Where have you been? We were looking for
you everywhere. I thought you were gone.
I'm not going anywhere, Fatma.
Sisters were going to wash
the clothes, I was with them.
And I got rid of some stress by helping them.
They got old a lit bit but that's alright.
Then, next time take me, too.
Of course.
We were afraid for our children
because of The Greek rebellion.
Thankfully, Gonca Hatun encouraged us.
Don't be upset! Don't be afraid!
This rebellion will be over soon, too!
We've seen many fights and battles.
The ones who caused this will not be upset.
Bad things will happen to our sons again.
Come on, sisters.
Come on, Gulce.
Daughter, don't be upset.
Where have you been all this time?
It took a long time to be healed.
I've seen the death very closely.
I waited inside the darkness.
I made a promise.
I was going to revive for revenge.
It took a long time to gather my army,
which will drown them in their blood.
My soldiers!
As you see...
My wish for getting revenge
from Osman revived me.
Death became my breath.
I became the death itself.
I won't only kill him.
I will destroy whatever Osman has in this world.
Sofia.
I am so glad you returned.
Our partnership...
...will be the bloodiest
alliance witnessed by history!
How could this happen Bayhan Bey?
How could he give the castle
we took with our swords?
Didn't we put our lives on
the line to take that castle?
Osman Bey must have a reason.
But I don't understand the reason behind it.
It must be politics.
I don't care about politics!
Bayhan Bey, this is not good!
Keep in mind...
...the herd of a blind
shepherd falls from a cliff!
Attention! Osman Bey!
Listen to me carefully now.
It's time to stop this rebellion.
The state shows its kind face sometimes...
..and when the time comes...
...it knows how to strike with its iron fist!
You will be sharper than
swords and tougher than steel.
Alaeddin.
You will go to Yenisehir.
As you command my Bey.
Orhan you will go to Sogut.
Gencer Bey, you will
defend your property, Mekece.
As you command my Bey.
Bayhan Bey.
You are responsible for Karacahisar's defence.
As you command my Bey.
If anyone starts a rebellion...
...or commits crimes, you will kill them!
As you command my Bey.
If anyone asks for forgiveness...
...I will decide their fate.
Either victory or death!
My Bey.
My Bey, as you asked, we
conducted an investigation in Sogut.
We caught this dog and made him talk.
The man with scarred face, he was
seen with Lucas. He started the rebellion.
Arcadeus!
Those who rule with blood..
...will be judged with blood.
Arcadeus, huh?
Every breath he takes...
...is a torment for me!
Boran.
My Bey.
Send word to Ilbay.
I will meet him near Karakaya.
As you command my Bey.
Everyone get back to your duties.
You don't understand what's going on.
You are a princess, that's why.
But don't worry.
I'll tell you how life
goes on in this tribe.
What do you mean Hazal Hatun?
I don't understand.
She provoked the people
against you on the first day.
Who?
Gonca?
Kayi Hatuns blame you for the rebellion.
Because Gonca Hatun poisons their minds.
She is taking her baby's revenge like that.
No.
You don't know Gonca well.
She wouldn't do that.
Allah cursed us.
How could you do this?
How could you?
They gave up the castle.
How could you do this?
Beys!
Sisters!
Osman Bey ordered...
...for Karadin Castle to be owned by Karesi Bey.
It's true.
It's still Turk territory.
Now, our part...
...is to clean up the mess
left from the uprisings.
Sogut uprising cost a lot.
Our first job is..
...to revive the bazaar...
...when the uprising ends.
We'll improve Sogut Bazaar.
If Allah permits!
The bazaar will help our trade
grow, if Allah permits.
If Allah permits!
When Osman Bey comes...
...he'll declare the owner of the bazaar.
You asked for me my Bey.
Tell me.
Where's the inn of the jackal Arcadeus?
He lives in the arena my Bey.
He trains gladiators.
He hosts feasts.
He lives and sleeps there.
Good.
We'll kill him in his bed.
My Bey.
Forgive me but...
...you can't easily enter the arena.
It has one entrance.
It's loaded with soldiers.
No excuses.
Not even walls or gates can stop us.
...will hit him in the safest place.
As you wish my Bey.
Brother. Arcedeus, or whatever he's called...
You said he hosts feasts.
He likes to have fun when he can.
But he's cautious.
His most trusted men wait by the gate.
Then search everyone.
They never let a sworded man in.
We can't fly in there.
You can't back down.
We have always..
...kept our word.
When did we not keep it?
We'll go inside, somehow.
Listen carefully.
Hazal Hatun was busy.
She told Holofira Hatun that
Gonca Hatun angered the people.
Hazal chose her side.
Let her.
Since they took the castle from me
she must be very happy right now.
But if I'm Begum then I won't
let both Hazal and Bala be happy.
I'll get the power
I've lost back.
May I come in Begum Hatun?
Gonca Hatun.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Osman Bey.
I've heard that he took Karadin Castle from you.
I wanted to see you.
Osman Bey did the right thing.
You tell me.
I've heard that the Kayi ladies
don't like the new bride here a lot.
You can use this for your advantage.
I'm sorry?
What are you saying Begum Hatun?
The people have already
turned their backs to Holofira.
Like her being a Christian isn't enough,
that riot happened because of her too.
So this means..
...both you and Alaeddin have better odds now.
Do whatever you can..
Stop there, Hatun.
I understand you.
But I have no intentions like that.
Gonca.
I'm saying this because I think of your future.
If you don't keep your eyes peeled...
...you'll always remain
as the wife of a Shahzade.
We're going through tough times, Begum Hatun.
I don't want the people to divide because of us.
Excuse me.
You'll become a wife to a bey
just with kindness and mercy huh?
Whether you want it or
not you're in war no Gonca.
Since Holofira has caused
a reaction with the people...
...use her Christianity...
...and the riot to fuel the fire.
Keep your eyes on them too.
As you wish Begum Hatun.
You'll be the one to get burned
the worst with this fire, Bala.
I'm going to take Alaeddin who
you call your first miracle from you.
Shahzade Orhan, the murderer of the father.
Attack brothers.
Shahzade Orhan, killer.
Aykurt.
Cover all the streets.
The Greek people and the
Turks won't see each other.
Cover the back, don't let anyone pass.
People.
For your and your belongings' sake...
...go to your homes right now.
You're a murderer.
You killed the father.
Alps.
Shield.
My Shahzade, he is not an
alp and he's not one of us either.
Lowlife. Oguz.
Oh Allah.
They're trying to egg them on.
They're giving out swords.
Killers.
What will we do now Shahzade?
First, we'll smash the head of the snake.
Baykurt, Turan, come with me. Come on.
Trader Marco.
Traitor Marco.
Dog Marco.
You're taking the people, you were
sharing your bread with, to the death, huh?
Look at my face
Orhan!
Now...
Now, you'll suffer the consequences, Marco.
Take him.
Get up!
Get up, get up.
You'll be punished for everything you did.
For everything!
Move! Move!
Move!
You, dog
Go down!
Come here.
I'm not the murderer!
It's this traitor dog, who
led you into rebellion!
They tried everything to provoke and agitate!
They didn't even hesitate to
kill their own religion brothers!
My Shehzade.
This cross was with the alp, who attacked you!
Hey people! Drop your
weapons! Stop the rebellion!
From now on...
...the state is here!
The ones who sow discord
among us have been punished!
I swear that no one will be harmed!
But from now on..
...if there is anyone who
rebels, anyone tries to backstab...
...he will be killed with my sword...
...like this dog.
Never forget this.
BURSA
I'm working in Bursa Palace. Here it is.
This trades is here for the show in arena.
They are the guests of Commander Lukas.
Greetings to the heroic
soldiers of Commander Lukas!
Greetings!
Send words to Arkadeus.
But...
...if Commander Lukas learns about
this, it won't be good for you at all.
Are you questioning their guests?
No! No! No! No! No!
They are just doing their job.
They keep the sacred
Bursa in security? Don't they?
Of course, they do.
Of course, that's right.
Petrus, commander Lucas
will not hear about this, right?
Please forgive us.
On the contrary.
I will tell commander Lucas that...
...we will have real fun with the special wine...
...I have brought for him, and
how we will reward them.
You deserve it.
You are embarrassing us, Petrus.
Please don't wait any longer.
You may pass.
Okay.
Spread everywhere. I want to know
how many soldiers are stationed here.
We will kill them tonight.
What's happening here?
Come on.
What are you doing? Come to your senses.
What is this?
Move.
Stop.
Come to your senses.
No one will get hurt.
Take the Turks away. Come on.
You're brothers, don't do
this. What are you doing?
Please. What is this?
Don't do this. Don't.
No!
Who is throwing the gunpowder?
Dastards!
Those are Arcadeus' men!
My shahzade!
Dastards!
Where do you think you are running!?
Come here!
I have arrived, my Shahzade.
Stay down
You are not rusty at all, Baysungur.
You have always been watching my back.
Thank you.
Killing dogs like him is
good practice, my shahzade.
God willing, I won't get rusty
as long as Allah allows me.
Alright.
Now you will talk.
-Get him up.
-Get up!
Move!
You will talk!
Enough! Shut up!
People, listen to me!
This dog is Arcadeus' man
Their intention is making
Turks and Greeks fight each other!
You are lying!
Lies!
Traitor Turk!
Know that..
...we didn't kill that priest!
Speak!
Speak so I will spare
your worthless life!
Speak!
Turks didn't kill him.
We did!
Arcadeus did it!
They tricked us!
In Osman Bey's property...
...your life and goods are in our protection.
Everyone is free to follow their own religion.
End this rebellion..
...and return to your homes.
Come on.
Come on hatuns.
I know you are doing your best, but...
...we should be faster, right?
Good day, Bala Hatun.
Good day, Begum Hatun.
Your carpets look pale.
If we can help...
Thanks, Begum Hatun.
I'll tell you if it's necessary.
But...
...I wish you showed the same importance
to things that doesn't concern you...
...to Karadiri castle.
Then the castle would still
be under your command.
And our trust in you wouldn't be shaken.
I don't think Osman Bey
doesn't trust me anymore.
He saw how much I cared for Karadin.
He congratulated me on the Hatuns I assigned...
...to keep the borders safe.
These Hatuns..
Are they the hatuns of your tribe?
I assigned them to stop the uprising.
If I hadn't, they'd have stopped Lukas.
Hold on.
How could you assign Hatuns...
...without my knowledge
and without proper training...
...prepared specially for The Sisters?
I trust them all.
Bala Hatun they are trained.
What's wrong with that?
This is the state's order Begum Hatun.
This is the state.
What would happen if anyone was assigned?
That is disorder.
Peace would vanish.
You made the second mistake.
You should know that.
First thing, you'll bring the hatuns here.
They will be trained.
If I see them fit,
they will be assigned.
I won't tolerate another weakness.
Know that.
We are the real masters of the empire.
Eat! Drink!
Victory will be ours!
My Bey, brother, come!
Come.
My Bey.
My Bey. Here.
Here are all the keys.
They will unlock all doors, with Allah's help.
Alright, Cerkutay, alright.
Come on Ibrahim. Open up.
Here my Bey.
Brother.
This is water.
What if the soldiers wanted to look inside?
What would we do then?
I put them in wine Boran Bey.
I poured the wine out brothers.
We can't dirty our holy swords with evil drinks.
Okay.
Okay Cerkutay.
You did well.
Come on.
Arcedous, or whatever the name..
He doesn't get
to live any longer.
We'll end this tonight. Let's go.
Kayi tribe
The uprising was stopped in many lands.
Thank Allah we're free of this trouble.
Thank Allah mother.
Thank Allah.
We stopped it, with Allah's help.
We shut those dastards
who incited the Greek people...
...to start the uprising.
But...
....Turks and Greeks were harmed.
We must offer help.
When we improve Sogut Market,
many people will be employed there.
And this will heal our people faster,
if Alalh permits.
If Allah permits, mother.
But...
...to ensure this never happens again...
...it is best to harm those
who harmed us mother.
All the places they've destroyed...
...they should rebuild them themselves.
Let it be a lesson.
Gonca is right, mother Bala.
Let those who destroyed
or even slightly caused this...
...shall rebuild them.
But don't let the owners
of the houses that were destroyed
take down what's
being rebuild as a lesson...
Both of my sister in laws are right.
They both thought well.
I think we should rebuild it together.
Right.
First us, this tribe...
We'll be together.
We'll dress our wounds together.
Our pain.
Our happiness.
We will share them just as we share this bread.
So that our people are united too.
Right?
Come on.
Damn Turks.
We will have fun...
...and you will die in poverty.
I'm going to kill you all.
I'm going to make you beg before you die.
You have to walk all over my dead body first.
But...
...you will die today.
Osman.
Osman, yeah.
You won't make it out alive.
Look here.
You brought harm to my lands.
You made my people turn against each other.
Now...
Now is the time you pay for it.
I'm going to hang you off of my arena.
Is that so?
Let's see.
Playing with a wolf...
...ends in blood.
Karadin..
It will be a stain in Osman's destiny.
And there will be no one
left who hasn't heard of this.
Everyone is talking about this my bey.
But I'm curious about something.
Why did Osman give Karadin to you my bey?
Because his honor was ruined.
His power has lessened.
There is no place for doubt in leadership.
He is trying to save it but...
...it's a meaningless effort.
What should we do about the taxes my bey?
Osman was getting 1/3 of what we get usually.
Has he gone mad?
That's not possible.
First and foremost,
Karadin's treasury will be filled.
Double the taxes.
As you wish my bey.
My Bey.
There is an important news, my Bey.
What is that important?
Osman Bey.
Osman Bey did it again, my
Bey. He suppressed the rebellion.
They say he'll improve
the bazaar and gain...
...income from the road
coming from China to Greeks.
If he can improve the bazaar...
...gold will rain in the Osman's lands.
He'll be stronger...
...and their people will trust Osman more.
What should we do, my Bey?
We'll prevent him from getting strong all alone!
We'll take our share from
the trade in Sogut Bazaar!
Arkadeus!
Who did this?
Who?
Who dared to kill my commander in my arena?
How did the infiltrate among you?
How?
Osman.
Osman!
I'll kill you!
These are his last moves, you'll see.
Soon...
...Osman will take his place.
Commander Lukas.
What is it?
Osman Bey suppressed the rebellion.
Worse, he decided to
revive the bazaar in Sogut.
They say he'll improve the
bazaar and gain more income.
How?
How could he suppress the rebellion? How?
So, he'll improve the bazaar.
How nice!
Then, I say we should
contribute to Osman's trade.
What do you say?
What do you have in your mind, Sofia?
Send words to Karasi Bey, Lukas.
I need to meet him.
KAYI TRIBE
Welcome, Osman Bey!
-Thankfully, my Bey!
-Welcome!
My Bey, welcome!
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
Are the missions successful?
As you ordered, my Bey. All the rebellions
in our lands have been suppressed.
Thank you.
May you be live long.
Osman Bey.
I heard you gave Karadin, for whom
my son sacrificed his life, to Karaca Bey.
Now, it means my son died for nothing!
Mother.
"Do not call those
who are killed in the way of Allah...
..."They are dead".
On the contrary.
Rather, they are alive."
[2:154]
Your son is a martyr, mother.
Not just for Karadin castle.
For the state, and for the
future of the true religion Islam.
Your son gave his life.
But his place...
...is right next to our great prophet PBUH.
Mother.
Tell me.
If I came to you and told you
that I am going for ghaza...
...but I have no soldiers
that can hold a weapon.
How would you answer?
I would take up arms
and come with you!
Thank you.
People! Tell me. What would you do?
We would come with you my Bey!
Thank you.
Since you believe me and trust me...
...then know this.
The reason I gave Karadin
castle to Karesi Bey is...
...for the...
...future of our state...
...just as your son who sacrificed himself.
Alright, my Bey.
Many tried to sow discord in our lands!
They started a rebellion after
provoking the non-Muslims!
But we have answered them all!
The one who lead them...
...the tool of that dog called Lucas...
...Arcadeus, we killed him
and hanged him on their castle!
Long live my Bey! Long live mysBey!,
Thanks to my Beys and my soldiers...
...we stopped the rebellions.
Those who sow discord lost their heads!
Both friends and enemies saw that...
...they cannot defeat us
with discord and treachery!
Either victory...
...or death!
Either victory or death!
The rebellion damaged the West and East
of Mekece most. Repair those areas first.
Then you will place the
people that moved into North.
You will bring the order back.
As you command my Bey.
Come on my lions!
Someone's coming
Let them come!
Who are you Hatun?
Do you have a permit to cross through my land?
My trade documents.
I'm Maria.
I am a merchant.
My trade network...
...lies from China and Constaninople.
So, you're here to trade.
You heard about the bazaar
Osman Bey will set in Sogut.
I heard about it.
But I'm not here for bazaar.
I want to trade with you.
I will pay you 3 times the price...
...for all of your goods.
Why me and not bazaar?
Bazaar means there's a
middle man. That will slow things.
I want to work with a supplier.
No middle man. I'll earn more.
...and so will he.
Come on in then. We'll talk about your offer.
You'll be our guest. Come.
Carry Maria Hatun's baggage.
Memorize all the entrances...
...the number of soldiers
and watchers in the castle.
Find the castle's biggest weakness.
Don't worry.
Here.
I admire..
...your everlasting ambition, Lucas.
I stopped you getting the
castle but you still wish to talk.
Politics can turn two friends into enemies.
It can also turn two enemies
into friends, Karesi Bey.
Yes you tricked me.
But being your enemy is
bad for me right now.
What will being your ally gain me?
Everything.
Osman will grow his trade.
This won't be good for either of us.
Right.
I wonder what you'll say.
I want you to give Osman a ship.
What are you saying?
Did you lose your mind?
You heard me Karesi Bey.
Give him a ship.
You'll make him take his
goods to other cities via ship.
He'll like this offer.
Then what?
Then I will blow up that ship.
All his goods will sink to the bottom.
You have truly lost your mind.
My ship doesn't sink.
This will cost me a lot.
I will pay...
...for all the damage, Karesi Bey.
Just give him the castle.
Tell me.
How will that plan go?
Hear me people!
Two brave men are in the battlefield.
Both of them are braver than the other.
A man needs to train, even if
it's training they need strength.
The rope will be pulled...
...and the stronger one will
knock down the weaker one.
May Allah give you strength.
Come on then.
Come on Saruca, knock them down.
Come on my lion son.
Don't worry mother.
I'm going to knock them down.
We'll see who will knock down who.
I support Turahan.
He is stronger than all of you.
Thank you Ghazi.
You're hurting us Ghazi.
Not at all, Sergeant Aykurt.
I'm just giving my opinion.
I even bet one gold coin
for uncle Turahan's side.
Heavens above!
Look at him go.
Will you be a gambler huh?
I can't reach your ear!
Where did you find gold?
Tell me right now.
Ulgen Hatun.
I gave it to him.
Told him to go and
get cloth for clothes.
Come on. I wish you all luck.
Allah.
-Oh Allah.
-Come on.
Come on.
Come on Saruca, come on.
-Pull it.
-Come on.
Come on uncle Turahan. Come on.
Come on, come on uncle Turahan.
-Come on Saruca.
-Pull it.
-Come on.
Come on.
-Oh Allah.
-Come on.
-Come on alps.
Oh Allah.
Come on, unIce Turahan.
Aykurt.
Uncle Turahan!
Come on Sergeant Aykurt!
-Come on.
-Oh Allah.
Come on.
-Come on.
-Pull it.
-Saruca.
-Come on.
Come on.
My Osman.
I've got food prepared for you.
Come, my bey.
Thank you Bala.
Thank you.
What is it?
What's that noise?
To change this negative mood
and to make the people a bit happy...
...I've told the alps to have a bit of fun.
You thought well Bala.
The people will of course feel better.
But the daughter in laws...
How will they be?
Gonca has focused on work
to forget about her pain, my bey.
She's okay.
And Holofira is a new bride,
she's trying to get used to the tribe.
She won't have a hard time
when she has you here, right dear?
I know all sides of you, but...
I don't know what kind of a mother in law
you are. Don't torture my daughter in laws.
Look at this.
What are you saying as if you don't know me?
Come on now Osman.
I know you well.
I do.
Of course.
Bala.
You'll be their guide.
What do they say?
A man is the pillar of a house,
and the woman the walls.
Now they too will be the rocks
our sons need.
Just as how I've raised our kids...
...I'm going to guide them too Osman.
Don't worry.
Now, excuse me.
Where are you going?
I'm teaching The Sisters.
If you like we can check up
on them together after you eat.
Okay then, we'll go together.
Okay.
Turahan.
-Come on Saruca.
-Come on.
Turahan.
-Uncle Turahan.
-Come on alps.
Aykurt.
-Uncle Turahan.
Come on Saruca.
Come on!
Come on, it's almost over!
Come on, Sarica!
Oh no, my son is going to lose!
He'll bring shame on us!
Come on now! Come on now!
-Come on! Come on now!
-Bey!
I can't stand!
Sarica, I'm coming!
I'll help you, Sarica!
-Pull!
-Stop!
Cheating! She's cheating!
Mother! What are you doing, mother?
Oh Allah!
Come on, Alps! Come on, Alps!
You see that, Ayse?
Look, my uncle Turan wins!
The winner, Yusuf Bey, Turahan...
...and Alps.
-Oh Praise be!
-Great!
Don't be upset, son. There
was injustice but you fought well.
My lion.
You brought shame on us and yourself.
Don't listen to your father.
My Bey.
You see, Fatma Hatun?
The weak ones lost.
We won.
Both sides fought well.
But there is only one winner, of course.
Are you okay, Sarica?
Come on, sisters!
All of our sister has been trained, Osman Bey.
Bala Hatun.
Okay.
I've trained my
sisters personally.
I learned this method from
a warrior coming from China.
China, huh?
Begum Hatun, you learned it wrong.
They learned it from our
ancestors, from Gokturks!
Bala, you see this?
They lay claim to everything.
Ours is better.
I can train your hatuns,
too, if you wish, Bala Hatun.
It's unnecessary, Begum Hatun.
Then, let's see it together
if it is unnecessary or not.
Come on Begum Hatun.
Come on Begum Hatun, is this all you got?
It would be rude to..
...disarm Osman Bey's
Hatun right in front of him.
None could disarm me until now, Begum Hatun.
I told you Begum Hatun.
Your fearlessness will cost you your life.
Be more careful.
Praise be, Bala.
Praise be.
You did a good job Begum Hatun.
But The Sisters are trained well.
No need for another method.
Know that.
Kismet.
I'm not like others, Bala.
I am patient.
I'll get to my goal even if I'm slow.
These are great Bayhan Bey.
You paid good money.
Where did you get these?
Don't touch.
Much of it will hurt your stomach.
Leave that aside now, you told
me you had an important agreement.
What's that?
It's an amazing one.
I'm going to make what
Begum Hatun makes in a week...
...in a day.
How will that be?
A Greek woman named Maria. A merchant.
She has amazing connections.
She gives supplies to caravans.
She doesn't mess with
the bazaar because she
doesn't want to give
money to the middle person.
She's a smart woman.
She is.
She is smart but...
...she is not just smart, Bayhan Bey.
She's very beautiful too.
Beautiful?
What kind of a woman is she?
Does she have a husband?
What is it Bayhan Bey? Why do you care if
she has a husband? What will you do with him?
I mean, I'm asking for...
Maybe we can do trade
together in the future too.
I mean she's smart and beautiful.
She might have a husband.
Or not, of course, I don't know.
I mean, I don't know her.
Who is that woman you're talking about?
Hatun...
Gencer Bey?
I mean...
What Hatun?
We were discussing trade with Gencer
Bey here. Weren't we, Gencer Bey?
We were.
My Bala, I told you to go easy but
you still sweated her.
She is still alive, she'll be thankful for that.
She was talking yesterday.
She said while you were patrolling
the borders, you praised her a lot.
She did her duty well, and I praised her.
Really?
Bala, she prepared the Sisters very well.
They came from every corner.
But Hatuns are not the same as The Sisters.
She got out of the rules
and I made her remember it.
Okay, okay.
If you made her remember, then it is okay.
Now, tell me.
After all that, we captured the castle, too.
She is ambitious.
She might make a mistake
with pain of her failure.
She showed weakness in the castle.
But what about trade, huh?
The trade of Sogut.
Now, we need to improve Sogut's Bazaar.
What do you think? Can she do it?
Begum...
...with the ambition of her failure,
she'll try harder for this mission.
But...
...I want to take care of her, my Bey.
Of course, of course.
Then, let's do this way.
You assign her duty personally.
My Bey, Karasi Bey is coming.
Let him come.
Peace be with you.
Peace be upon you Karesi Bey.
Come..
...let's go to the tent so we can talk.
Your trade will vanish..
...just like snow in a desert, Osman.
Gonca Hatun.
Do you know why she summoned us?
My mother will announce whom
she gave the Sogut's management.
Good day.
From now on, Sogut bazaar's management...
...is under Begum Hatun.
Congratulations.
Come on then, everyone back to work.
Come with me Begum Hatun.
The duty is yours now.
You feel embarrassed..
...because you couldn't manage...
...the castle.
I know.
I know you won't repeat the same mistake and...
...fulfill your duty in the bazaar.
You can be rest assured, Bala Hatun.
Take a seat Karesi Bey.
Thank you but
I haven't come to sit and chat.
It's been a while since yesterday.
I was wondering why Karesi Bey did not show up.
You should know that Osman..
...Karesi Bey wouldn't...
...face anyone without a reason.
No doubt.
Tell me, what's the situation
in Karadin where I gifted you.
Karadin that you gifted
to deny our greatness...
...and overshadow our help...
...is in a good condition, Osman Bey.
The situation is good.
Tell me.
What brought you...
...here?
I heard that...
...you want Sogut to be the biggest...
...bazaar in the region.
When I wanted to have a share in the
land trade, you destroyed the bridge...
...and ruined my agreement with the Byzantine.
So I am saying that
even if we can't be allies...
...let's do some business together.
Do you want to send caravans to Sogut?
But that's not enough.
To sell my goods...
...I want a stall in the
bazaar to sell my goods.
I will pay you for it.
If you accept...
...I will give you one of my ships...
...with its crew and captain.
Your goods will be sold across
the sea, all over the world...
...not just the bazaar in Sogut.
Is that so?
We couldn't..
..unite our armies.
We were never allies.
Let's unite in trade then.
Finally you hold the hand I raise.
You made the best choice.
Our real enemy is the infidel.
With this trading union...
...Byzantines will lose
all their money, if Allah permits.
Now...
...gather all your goods in 3 days.
We'll send your goods...
...to the provinces I agreed
to trade with via your new ship.
-Thank you.
-It's alright.
Boran.
My Bey.
Sogut.
The tribes.
Karacahisar, Mekece...
Send word to all the people.
Everyone will gather the goods.
As you wish my Bey.
Kayi Tribe.
May I come in my Bey?
Come in Orhan.
My Bey.
As you wished, my Bey.
The caravan left.
We're ready to head out.
Alright son.
Alright.
Tell me what's on your mind.
My Bey.
I never intend to question
the decision you made.
But I worry that Karesi might
be on to something again.
Look.
I know why you suspect him.
Karesi Bey might do something.
But...
...do you know what really matters?
The politics.
I made this agreement for the people.
What do you mean my Bey?
In front of the people and the Beys...
...we held Karesi Bey's hand.
We proved that...
We're not the ones disrupting peace.
So you're saying, my Bey, if
Karesi Bey makes a mistake...
...the people and the Beys
will make him pay for it.
Exactly.
He can set a trap.
He can do as he wishes.
Don't forget.
Allah is the Best of those Who sets Traps.
By the way...
...keep this up.
Always keep suspecting.
The state lives off on suspicion.
Yes, my Bey.
3 days later
Shame...
It will be a shame...
I've build this ship myself.
If what I'm going to gain
was lesser than it's worth...
...I wouldn't be able to do this.
Whatever, Sancar.
Yes my bey.
Is everything ready?
Good.
We'll be hitting two birds with one stone.
Osman.
Such a simple man such as you...
How did you dare think you can defeat me?
Soon enough all of your
goods will be feed for the fish.
Your dreams will sink to the bottom of the sea.
My bey.
Osman Bey is coming.
Peace be with you.
Peace be upon you.
Welcome Osman Bey.
Welcome.
Thank you Karesi Bey.
Welcome to you too lad.
My Shahzade Alaeddin told me the rest of
the goods have been loaded into the ship.
Now you tell me it's going to sail off, huh?
It's ready.
It's waiting for your sign to sail.
This ship which is the mark of our agreement...
...shall sail with you.
You had so much that is
ready to be sold off, Osman Bey.
This is my biggest ship.
Your goods wouldn't fit in
my other ships.
I don't like to trade small.
If I'm going to throw a stone then
let it be worth the pain of throwing it.
Yes.
Let it be worth it.
Come on then.
Give them the sign, Osman Bey.
In the name of Allah.
Just as those sails are filled with wind...
...our treasuries will be filled too.
How could this be?
Karesi Bey.
What is this?
That's it.
Victory is mine.
It always has been.
What is this?
All of our goods.
We loaded them all on that ship.
What is this?
All those goods, all that hard work.
They're all ruined now.
If you lost your goods...
...then I've lost my ship Osman.
That doesn't concern me.
You will pay for this.
I won't be one paying Osman.
I'm going to make people pay.
Look at me.
Then..
..you will bring me whoever
that is responsible for this.
Yes.
Let's go, Sancak. Come on
Let's see the booty left from Osman!
Let's see, my Bey, let's see.
You'll lose everything Osman.
You'll lose everything
I won't sleep before I finish you, Osman.
When we return, we'll prepare
a great celebration, Hristo.
Dastard!
Hatuns, may it be easy.
The caravans set out quickly thanks to you.
Great job.
May it be easy, sisters.
-Thank you, Gonca.
-Welcome.
New threads for the carpets have arrived.
Let's start with those together, huh?
Let's decorate Sogut with
our colorful carpets! Come on.
Come on, let's start.
Holofira daughter.
You still don't believe me, do you?
I told you, look! She
provokes people against you.
-Why would she do that?
-For his man.
You should take care of your husband and
make good connections with people at once.
It's hard when there is Gonca but..
Do you know her mother, Saadet?
I saw her once, but oh! She was disgusting!
She is just like her mother.
You don't want to cause any enmity but they
start to think badly about Orhan because of you.
No.
I can't let them harm Orhan.
Look, how happy they are!
Sisters.
Put what you have in your hands
down for a minute. Listen to me.
Why did you treat Holofira like that?
We don't feel like it, Gonca Hatun. She
is not one of us anyway. She is Christian.
And the rebellion started because of her.
-Don't act like this, sisters. Holofira...
-Gonca.
You said Holofira.
What were going to say about me?
-I told sisters...
-You...
...said the friendship
was over, and I said okay.
I thought you were in pain
but this is too much, Gonca.
I don't understand.
What did I do to you?
You deny it now? It's a shame.
-I can't even recoginize you anymore.
-Holofira!
Do you hear your words?
What did I do to you?
You... You blamed me for
nothing. I didn't say a word.
But I've understood your intention, Gonca.
Gonca! Holofira!
Come to the tent.
Here!
Osman's goods.
Osman lost his reputation and his goods.
This damaged his treasury...
...and the trust of his people in him, my Bey.
Then the only person they will trust will be me!
Me!
They think their chests are in the sea..
...but they will never know
that we changed the chests.
A Bey should always hit
two birds with one stone.
When the night comes, you
will load the goods to the ships.
As you command my Bey.
Open the chests.
Let's see how rich Osman made me.
My Bey, there is only stones and hay!
What?
What's going on my Bey? Where are the goods?
Osman!
Black Osman!
He realized everything!
My Bey.
Yes, Cerkutay? Speak.
I would sacrifice a lot to
see Karesi Bey's face...
...when he opens the chests.
You should have allowed
me to sneak in and hide...
...and watch the shape his face takes.
We made great Karesi Bey
carry chests filled with stones.
He will never forget this lesson.
May brother Baysungur
long live. He did a good job.
That's right.
You were right my Bey.
Karesi Bey is working with that dog Lucas.
Their intention is to sink
our ship with the goods.
Are you sure?
I am sure,my Bey. I saw it with my own eyes.
Lucas' men gave Karesi Bey's alps gunpowder.
Alps placed the gunpowder secretly in our ship.
Baysungur.
You did a great job.
We will see now...
...whose goods will be
blown and whose ship will sink.
Baysungur saved our state from a great loss.
Long live my brave man.
My Bey, Alaeddin must have secured the goods.
The goods should wait a little longer.
When the time comes, we will make the caravan.
Now let's see...
...what will Baysungur learn from Lucas.
That's what's important.
Come on.
Karesi Bey.
The goods will stay here for a little longer.
Secure the place.
Put scouts everywhere.
The alps are on their places, my Bey.
Good, eyyAllah.
Come on then. We are going to the tribe.
Speed up!
What are you up to, you snake!?
Sofia?
You...
How?
How? Devil!
I'm no devil. I'm here to kill you.
Your spies are all dead.
I crushed your network of intelligence.
In Bursa..
...Nikea...
...and the rest of our cities.
...I killed all of your spies...
...that had the red tailed pigeon.
You're lying.
My brothers.
Now...
...like the rest of them...
...you'll die too.
Only Allah knows that.
All of you will fall by my sword one by one.
I'll cut out your hearts.
Those...
...who work with the devil..
...eventually...
...faces a devil.
Devil.
Come here. Come here.
It won't be that easy.
Allah. In the name of Allah.
Allah.
Take him to Osman.
He'll take his last breath next to him.
Take him.
All of your spies are dead Osman.
After this much damage,
you'll only dream of conquest.
Tell me what's happening?
What's happening that you
fight in front of the people?
I don't know mother.
You have to ask Holofira.
She is the one who caused it out of nowhere.
So you don't know huh?
Did you start to lie too Gonca?
Hatun.
Come to your senses.
You've been provoking the people against
me ever since the day I came to the tribe.
What?
What does that mean girl?
Mother!
The people turned their back to me.
Just because I'm a Christian.
They hold me responsible for the Greek riot too.
Since Gonca is mad at me she
is provoking them against me.
Holofira.
Hear what you're saying.
Is this true Gonca?
Mother?
Do you believe this?
I didn't believe it either.
But I saw it.
You are...
...just as bad as
your ill-souled mother.
Holofira.
Mother.
Do you think so?
No, there's something wrong. It's clear.
Listen to me well.
Holofira.
I'll take care of the people.
But I don't want anything akin to
what happened today to happen again.
Come to your senses.
You are Kayi's daughters in law.
People are watching you.
Not just them. The enemies
who want to defeat us, destroy us.
You are the first people they will go to.
My sons are the wings of this nation.
And you, the supporters of those wings.
From now on..
...you will act accordingly.
I don't want to see any
mistakes from both of you.
The first thing those who
wish to hurt this nation...
...will do is to rip it's wings.
But as long as I'm alive...
...I will never let that happen.
How...
How did he know?
Where are Osman's goods?
Osman Bey sent chests
filled with stones and hay.
We don't know where he placed the goods.
Osman.
Are you taking out your anger Lucas?
Osman emptied all of his goods out. All of them.
Karesi.
We gave him gold for nothing.
I swear...
...he will pay the price he
made me pay with his blood.
Calm down.
We are the strong ones.
Losing gold is not a problem
if it helps us to eliminate Osman.
I've sent him a gift he won't forget.
He'll be receiving it any moment now.
What?
I've cut Osman's arteries.
I've destroyed his network from
which he gathered information.
A bey that has...
...no eyes or ears...
...anywhere.
What can he do now?
You...
You..
You're a genius.
Sofia.
Osman Bey is coming.
-Welcome my bey.
-Osman Bey.
-Welcome Bey.
-Welcome my bey.
May Allah give you a long life my bey.
-Welcome.
Welcome Osman Bey.
Osman Bey.
Did the ship that's carrying
our goods sail safe and sound?
When it departed...
..they shot the ship with
The Greek Fire and sunk it.
What? Did the ship sink?
All of our hard work gone to waste...
Who is the one that has done this Osman Bey?
The ones who always harmed us
all this time.
But...
...we knew about our enemy's plans
beforehand and took every precaution.
Don't worry.
All of the goods are safe.
What has sunk to the bottom of that sea...
...is our enemy’s nerve.
-Long live Osman bey.
-Long live Osman Bey.
Long live Osman Bey.
Someone's coming.
Is that Baysungur?
Baysungur is coming. He is injured.
Baysungur...
Who did this?
Let me go, I'll go to my bey.
Who did this Baysungur?
Hurry up, come on!
Make way.
How could it be, my Bey?
Baysungur.
Baysungur!
Baysungur! Baysungur!
-Baysungur!
-My brother!
Baysungur!
Come on. Come here, my warrior.
What is this?
-Baysungur! Baysungur!
Baysungur.
Who did this, huh?
Tell me, my warrior, who
did this? Who did this to you?
My time has come, my Bey.
Don't talk like that. Don't
talk like that, Baysungur.
Brother, don't do it! No! No! No!
You're not going! You are not leaving!
Baysungur, my lion brother.
No! Hang on! Hang on!
Come on, we are going to
the healing tent! Alps! Help me!
Baysungur, hang on.
I'm going to The Righteous, my Bey.
My Bey.
The box, my Bey.
Wait, hang on!
Hang on! Baysungur!
Our spies...
They martyred them my Bey!
May our state last forever.
May...
May a thousand...
...Baysungurs...
...sacrifice themselves for you.
Who did this?
Who did this? Lukas? Karasi Bey?
Tell me. Who did this to you?
Who did this?
Sop...
Tell me! Who did this?
I bear witness that there is none
worthy of worship except Allah...
Don't do it, brother.
...and I bear witness that
Mohammad is His servant...
..and messenger.
Baysungur!
My lion brother!
Indeed, we belong to Allah, and
Indeed, to Him, we shall return.
My warrior.
Don't you worry.
I'll take your revenge.
I swear, the people who
did this to you will pay dearly!
I am going to kill them all! All of them!